premiumize.me 2015-03-18

# Premiumize.me, All-In-One Cloud-Downloading

## Über

We offer a service that essentially enables the user to use our servers to perform the very same tasks that would normally be executed locally on his computer.

However, since the downloading, accessing files and media is handled remotely on our servers (“in the cloud”), the user will greatly benefit from the servers connectivity to the internet.

The user is able benefit through our aggregated premium connections to many different websites and datacenters. This results in higher speed and conveneince.

back to top

Please [click here](http://www.google.com/recaptcha/mailhide/d?k=01mgr0HFx99plfNdWUnuI5TA==&c=NWRWaY3_fWPCkm9r4GvQ5aIIrSh3U1_SauLcQRRMzV4=) for our email.

To avoid spam, you have to enter a captcha to reveal it.

If you are a member and are searching for support, please [click here](https://dev.premiumize.me/help) to reach our support.

For direct legal contact and address information please refer to our imprint.

back to top

## Terms of service

### premiumize Terms & Conditions

Please read the following terms. Usage of premiumize.me constitutes agreement with these terms. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site.

premiumize is a web service. The service is offered as is. premiumize will always make reasonable effort to migitate any service problems. premiumize cannot give warranty on the function or reliability of foreign websites or services where said offered product might be used.

premiumize provides you on its website premiumize.me with a service to optimize your internet speed and usage of supported websites. premiumize reserves the right to add and remove services to its supported service list at its own discretion. The owner explicitly states, that there is no guarantee that any given service can be supported for the duration of the whole membership term time- however will always try with due diligence to expand, not reduce, the customer experience.

Premiumize.me reserves the right to block a user account if there is abuse on the system. Abuse is for example, but not limited to, one of the following: 

  * shared login access by shared login data 
  * shared login access by other means like through server or vpn access 
  * usage of account with several IPs in short time period (TOR, VPN Access) 
  * purchasing several memberships to circumvent account limitations 
  * create several accounts to circumvent the trial restrictions or affiliate program 
  * reselling premiumize.me access without the prior consent 
  * accessing illegal webpages, especially, but not limited to: terrorism, online crime, child pornography

Once blocked, it is in sole discretion of premiumize.me to remove the account block. In case of a blocked account, there is no refund possible.

premiumize has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by premiumize. Use of any such linked web site is at the users own risk.

Members are responsible for keeping their login information confidential. Furthermore, lost login information due to using "1minute", "trashmail" and similair web services will not be able to be restored. Premiumize.me asks you to use a reliable email provider for the signup process.

To process a payment we may ask you to provide information that personally identifies you or is otherwise personally identifiable in certain circumstances. Examples of personal information are your name, billing address, phone number and email. We use your personal information for two primary purposes:

  1. To help process your order, contact you, and help with any problems during and after the order process
  2. To alert you to special offers, updated information, and security issues

Orders require the customer to pay a one-time fee. The customer hereby authorizes premiumize to charge the users’ credit card or any other accepted payment method to pay for the membership. Please refer to our seperate refund policy found at the website.

premiumize is not liable for the actions of its payment service providers.

In no event shall the web service provider or his suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the service on premiumize.me, even if the owner or an authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

The materials appearing on the web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. The owner does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. premiumize may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. premiumize may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice.

Any claim relating to the owers web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Belize without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

back to top

## Refund Policy and Money Back Guarantee

Payments for services are non-refundable and final in all but the most exceptional cases (fraud, crucial typing error).

Refund requests are handled on a case-by-case basis and only provided in the same form and same currency as the initial payment was made. It will appear on your credit card or bank statement within 10 business days.

Refunds for blocked accounts (please refer to Terms of Service) are not possible.

Requests for refund should be requested at our customer service 

Your request will be reviewed within 2 business days.

back to top

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which premiumize collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the premiumize.me website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by premiumize.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities, mainly our ability to process orders.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our site may use "cookies" to enhance user experience. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site, especially the browser plugins, may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

premiumize may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To process payments we may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. - To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send user information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the site and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

### Changes to this privacy policy

premiumize has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

back to top

## Customer Service

Our customer service can be found on the following page:

www.premiumize.me/help

back to top

## Imprint
